

BHAGYESH KHALODE

Full Stack Web Developer

My Contact

sonukhalode627@gmail.com

+91 7507030047

Amravati, Maharashtra

in <u>LinkedIn</u>

GitHub

Portfolio

Technical Skills

- React JS
- · Java Script
- Html
- CSS
- DBMS

Soft Skills

- Observation
- · Decision making
- Remote Work
- Adaptability

Education Background

Full Stack Web Development

Masai School, Bangaluru May 2022-present

Bachelor's in Mechanical Engineering

Sant Gadge Baba Amravati University, Maharasshtra

June 2015-june 2019

• Deploma In Mechanical Engineering

Maharashtra State Board of Technical Education

June 2012-June 2015

Interests

- Cooking
- Reading

Professional Summary

An ambitious and self-motivated web developer with considerable technical skills who possesses self-discipline & ability to work with minimum supervision. Able to play a key role in website development to ensure maximum accessibility, user experience & usability. A quick learner who can absorb new ideas & can communicate clearly & effectively.

Projects

Kickstarter.com Clone | ()

The Kickstarter website exists to help bring creative projects to life. A home for film, music, art, theater, games, comics, design, photography, and more.

Features:

- · Authentication for the website.
- Filter Products Category wise.
- Sort Products according to Price range

Key responsibilities:

- Build authentication functionality for the whole website.
- Build UI for Food & Craft page on the clone website.
- Build UI for Music page on the clone website.

Tech Stack: html, Java Script, CSS A collabrative project build by a 5 team members

<u>Lyst.com Clone</u>

Lyst is a legit clothing store. They have a wide variety of clothes and accessories for men, women, and children.

Features:

- Authentication for the website.
- Filter Products Category wise.
- Sort Products according to Price range

Key responsibilities:

- · Build authentication functionality for the whole website.
- Build UI for Men's page on the clone website.
- Build UI for Products page on the clone website.

Tech Stack: html, Java Script, CSS A collabrative project build by a 5 team members

Professional Experience

Manidip Engineering | Site Engineer

Responsibility: Boiler operations, maintenance, Coal handling plant maintenance, Man power handling

Sept-2019-April 2021

Morarjee Textile Industry.pvt.ltd | <u>Trainee Engineer</u>

Responsibility: Machine maintenance, Utility operations

Sept-2019-April 2021